嘿 快看啊
Hey, check it out...
我刚把丽芙的牙刷卖给了《放声歌唱》的粉丝
I sold Liv's toothbrush to a "Sing it Loud!" Fan
得到了一堆黏糊糊的眼球糖
and got us a bunch of gummy eyeballs.
真可惜  她只有一把牙刷
Too bad she only has one toothbrush.
哦  开玩笑呢吧  那把牙刷是我在人行道边上捡的
Oh, please... I picked that one off the sidewalk out front.
呃
Oh...
姐妹身份对调开始了
The switch-a-Rooney was on.
我花了四个小时来烫头发
It took me four hours to do my hair
而且丽芙要让我把头晾在床外睡觉
and Liv made me sleep with my head hanging off the mattress
来确保不把头发给压回去了
to protect the pouf.
我的口水甚至流到我鼻子里了
I drooled into my own nose.
非常感谢各位光临
Thank you all so much for coming
第四季的《放声歌唱》
to the season 4 DVD signing
光盘签售会
of  Sing it Loud!
亚蒂来了
Artie's here.
好戏开场了
Let the games begin.
丽芙·鲁尼
Liv Rooney.
近日有流言说你
Are the rumors true that you,
一个黄毛丫头  要饰演特里斯坦·莱肯
a girl, might play Tristan Lycanth?
流言是真的  脑残粉
It's true, fanboy.
你还有意见了
What say you?
我的意见是这是罪恶滔天不可饶恕的
I say it's intergalactic blasphemy!
而我会证明你根本不值得演这个角色
And I shall prove you're unworthy.
注意一下  我的小喽啰们在网络直播呢
Be warned my minions are live blogging.
网址是  伟大的亚蒂王@狼圈.嗷呜
King_Artie_the_magnificent @ wolfspot dot howl.
哈哈
Ha ha.
放马过来吧  亚蒂王
Bring it on, king Artie.
说说特里斯坦的血统吧
Speak for Tristan's lineage.
他的父母是谁
Who are his parents?
丽芙马上要出大丑啦
Liv is about to go down in flames.
他的父母
His parents
是狼人马格洛
are the werewolf Magrol
和赛拉女王
and queen Zira.
哈  咋样
Bam! What?!
我是说  真是个妙绝了的好问题啊
I mean, space-tastic question.
原来是玛蒂
Maddie.